[{"Response":"Got worse","Percent":49.3,"Question":"Compared with this time last year, do you think that your personal financial circumstances have improved, stayed the same or got worse?","Time period":2022},{"Response":"Stayed the same","Percent":28.7,"Question":"Compared with this time last year, do you think that your personal financial circumstances have improved, stayed the same or got worse?","Time period":2022},{"Response":"Improved","Percent":19.9,"Question":"Compared with this time last year, do you think that your personal financial circumstances have improved, stayed the same or got worse?","Time period":2022},{"Response":"Very difficult","Percent":6.8,"Question":"Over the next year, how easy or difficult do you think it will be for your household to pay for the following? - Food -","Time period":2022},{"Response":"Difficult","Percent":9.6,"Question":"Over the next year, how easy or difficult do you think it will be for your household to pay for the following? - Food -","Time period":2022},{"Response":"Fairly difficult","Percent":10.8,"Question":"Over the next year, how easy or difficult do you think it will be for your household to pay for the following? - Food -","Time period":2022},{"Response":"Fairly easy","Percent":31.2,"Question":"Over the next year, how easy or difficult do you think it will be for your household to pay for the following? - Food -","Time period":2022},{"Response":"Easy","Percent":20.0,"Question":"Over the next year, how easy or difficult do you think it will be for your household to pay for the following? - Food -","Time period":2022},{"Response":"Very easy","Percent":17.5,"Question":"Over the next year, how easy or difficult do you think it will be for your household to pay for the following? - Food -","Time period":2022},{"Response":"Very difficult","Percent":18.0,"Question":"Over the next year, how easy or difficult do you think it will be for your household to pay for the following? - Energy (electricity\/gas) -","Time period":2022},{"Response":"Difficult","Percent":13.1,"Question":"Over the next year, how easy or difficult do you think it will be for your household to pay for the following? - Energy (electricity\/gas) -","Time period":2022},{"Response":"Fairly difficult","Percent":17.7,"Question":"Over the next year, how easy or difficult do you think it will be for your household to pay for the following? - Energy (electricity\/gas) -","Time period":2022},{"Response":"Fairly easy","Percent":25.1,"Question":"Over the next year, how easy or difficult do you think it will be for your household to pay for the following? - Energy (electricity\/gas) -","Time period":2022},{"Response":"Easy","Percent":13.7,"Question":"Over the next year, how easy or difficult do you think it will be for your household to pay for the following? - Energy (electricity\/gas) -","Time period":2022},{"Response":"Very easy","Percent":8.8,"Question":"Over the next year, how easy or difficult do you think it will be for your household to pay for the following? - Energy (electricity\/gas) -","Time period":2022},{"Response":"Very difficult","Percent":10.7,"Question":"Over the next year, how easy or difficult do you think it will be for your household to pay for the following? - Rent\/Mortgage -","Time period":2022},{"Response":"Difficult","Percent":11.4,"Question":"Over the next year, how easy or difficult do you think it will be for your household to pay for the following? - Rent\/Mortgage -","Time period":2022},{"Response":"Fairly difficult","Percent":17.1,"Question":"Over the next year, how easy or difficult do you think it will be for your household to pay for the following? - Rent\/Mortgage -","Time period":2022},{"Response":"Fairly easy","Percent":25.0,"Question":"Over the next year, how easy or difficult do you think it will be for your household to pay for the following? - Rent\/Mortgage -","Time period":2022},{"Response":"Easy","Percent":12.4,"Question":"Over the next year, how easy or difficult do you think it will be for your household to pay for the following? - Rent\/Mortgage -","Time period":2022},{"Response":"Very easy","Percent":8.3,"Question":"Over the next year, how easy or difficult do you think it will be for your household to pay for the following? - Rent\/Mortgage -","Time period":2022}]